<!DOCTYPE GWML>
<game>
	<locations>
		<location>
			<name>
				Living Room
			</name>
			<description>
				You are in your living room.
				A single lazy-boy recliner sits against the wall, and an
				aging TV sits across from it.
				Takeout containers and beer cans litter	the ground.
				Some items sit on the desk in the corner.
				Sunlight seeps in through a crack in the window drapes.
				
				There is a door leading to the BEDROOM behind you.
				There is a door leading OUTSIDE to your right.
			</description>
			<id>
				livingRoom
			</id>
			<items>
				<item>
					<name>
						Keys
					</name>
					<description>
						Your house KEYS, and the KEYS to your office.
					</description>
					<use>
						You use the keys.
					</use>
					<mass>
						1
					</mass>
					<type>
						1
					</type>
					<value>
						0
					</value>
				</item>
				<item>
					<name>
						Wallet
					</name>
					<description>
						A worn leather WALLET that holds your id, Bank Card,
						and whatever loose change you happen to have.
					</description>
					<use>
						You try to use your wallet.
					</use>
					<mass>
						1
					</mass>
					<type>
						1
					</type>
					<value>
						0
					</value>
				</item>
				<item>
					<name>
						Pass
					</name>
					<description>
						A plain lanyard that holds your work security PASS.
					</description>
					<use>
						You use the Security Pass.
					</use>
					<mass>
						1
					</mass>
					<type>
						1
					</type>
					<value>
						0
					</value>
				</item>
				<item>
					<name>
						Remote
					</name>
					<description>
						A black, cheap plastic REMOTE that came with the TV.
					</description>
					<use>
						Nothing happens. Your T.V. has been broken for months.
					</use>
					<mass>
						1
					</mass>
					<type>
						2
					</type>
					<value>
						0
					</value>
				</item>
			</items>
			<connects>
				none
				house
				bedroom
				none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					This should never be triggered.	
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
				Bedroom
			</name>
			<description>
				You are in your bedroom.
				Your eyes take some time to adjust to the darkness.
				A single-size mattress lays in the corner with a rough woolen blanket
				tossed across it. Clothes lay piled on the floor.
				A digital alarm	clock lays on the floor beside
				the mattress flashing '12:00'.
				
				The door to your LIVING ROOM is behind you.
				The EN SUITE BATHROOM is to your left.
			</description>
			<id>
				bedroom
			</id>
			<items>
				<item>
					<name>
						Clothes
					</name>
					<description>
						Your CLOTHES for the day; Business casual attire, but
						slightly stained and very rumpled.
					</description>
					<use>
						You put on your clothes.
					</use>	
					<mass>
						2
					</mass>
					<type>
						0
					</type>
					<value>
						5
					</value>
				</item>
				<item>
					<name>
						Blanket
					</name>
					<description>
						A rough woolen BLANKET.
					</description>
					<use>
						You wrap yourself in the blanket. It's warm, but now you're itching everywhere.
					</use>
					<mass>
						2
					</mass>
					<type>
						0
					</type>
					<value>
						3
					</value>
				</item>
			</items>
			<connects>
				none
				none
				livingRoom
				bathroom
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					This should never be triggered.	
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
				Bathroom
			</name>
			<description>
				Despite the state of the rest of the house, your
				bathroom is surprisingly clean. Nothing else to remark.
				
				The door back to your BEDROOM is behind you.
			</description>
			<id>
				bathroom
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				none
				none
				bedroom
				none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					This should never be triggered.	
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
				House
			</name>
			<description>
				You are outside your house.
				In front of you is a small, one story building with fading white clapboard and
				shingles beginning to peel off.
				There is a dead flower garden flanking the front steps.
				The whole place has definitely seen better days.
				
				Your front door is in front of you.
				The road and bus stop are behind you, down your short driveway.
			</description>
			<id>
				house
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
			livingRoom
			none
			busStop
			none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					CLOTHES
					You should probably put some clothes on. 
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
				Bus Stop
			</name>
			<description>
				Just as you take a seat to wait for the bus, it comes into 
				view and lurches to a violent stop with a screech of rubber.
				
				The bus to your OFFICE BUILDING is ahead of you.
				Your HOUSE is behind you.
			</description>
			<id>
				busStop
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				officeExterior
				none
				house
				none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					WALLET
					You have no way to to pay for you bus fare.
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
			Office Exterior
			</name>
			<description>
				You reach the outside of your office building, an unassuming
				five storey structure.
				
				The front ENTRANCE is in front of you.
				The BUS STOP is behind you.
				The PARK is to your right.
				The CAFE is to your left.
			</description>
			<id>
				officeExterior
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				officeLobby
				park
				busStop
				cafe
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					This should never be triggered
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
				Park
			</name>
			<description>
				You decide to head over to the city park, only a block away 
				from your office building. In fact, you can actually see it out of your office window.
				It's well kept with plenty of places to	sit and reflect. 
				The main attraction is a tranquil pond located centrally that is home 
				to countless ducks and geese.
				
				Your OFFICE BUILDING is to your right, back down the road. 
			</description>
			<id>
				park
			</id>
			<items>
				<item>
					<name>
						Stick
					</name>
					<description>
						A small STICK fallen from the branch of a tree.
					</description>
					<use>
						You hit yourself with the stick. It hurts. What did you expect?
					</use>
					<type>
						0
					</type>
					<mass>
						1
					</mass>
					<value>
						1
					</value>
				</item>
			</items>
			<connects>
				none
				officeExterior
				none
				none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					Shouldn't be triggered
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
				Cafe
			</name>
			<description>
				You arrive at the cute little cafe a short walk from your office building.
				The sun is shining nicely today, and the combination of 
				sunlight spreading across the outdoor seating area and the smell
				of roasting coffee is rather pleasant.
				
				Your OFFICE BUILDING is to your left, back down the road. 				
			</description>
			<id>
				cafe
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				none
				none
				none
				officeExterior
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					Shouldn't be triggered
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>	
		<location>
			<name>
				Office Lobby
			</name>
			<description>
				You tap your security pass to the sensor and enter the lobby of your office building.
				The interior is overly air-conditioned, and goosebumps
				immediatly start to form on your arms. Ahead of you is metal-detecting 
				archway with a sign reminding you to empty your pockets of metallic objects before passing through. 
				Your items will be waiting for you on the other side.
				
				The ARCHWAY is in front of you.
				The EXIT is behind you.
			</description>
			<id>
				officeLobby
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				officeSecurity
				none
				officeExterior
				none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					PASS
					You don't have your security pass on you and consequently can't enter the building. 
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
				Office Security
			</name>
			<description>
				You pass through to the other side of the scanner.
				
				The MAIN ATRIUM opens up in front of you.
			</description>
			<id>
				officeSecurity
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				officeAtrium
				none
				none
				none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_NOT_HAVE
					KEYS
					You left your keys in your pocket, and the alarm goes of. What did you expect?
					Try again.
				</trigger>
				<trigger>
					MUST_NOT_HAVE
					WALLET
					You left your wallet in your pocket, and the alarm goes of. What did you expect?
					Try again.
				</trigger>
				<trigger>
					MUST_NOT_HAVE
					REMOTE
					For some reason you had your TV Remote on you, and the alarm goes of. What did you expect?
					Try again.
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
				Office Atrium
			</name>
			<description>
				You step out into a grand atrium. The exterior of the building certainly doesn't let on the 
				grandeur contained within. A domed glass skylight lets golden rays of sun spill across the central
				waiting area. The walls and supporting columns appear to be made of a milky white marble with golden
				inlays in intricate patterns. Looking up, you can see balconies encircling the open area for each of the 
				five stories. It really is an impressive sight to behold. 
				
				In front of you is the RECEPTION DESK.
				Behind you is the way you came in, through the SECURITY CORRIDOR.
				To your left are the main floor WASHROOMS.
				To your right is the ELEVATOR up to the floor that your office is on.
			</description>
			<id>
				officeAtrium
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				officeReception
				officeElevator
				officeSecurity
				officeWashrooms
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					Shouldn't be triggered
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
				Office Reception
			</name>
			<description>
				You walk up to the reception area. Normally a sweet younger lady sits behind the 
				solid marble counter, greeting newcomers. Today however, the entire atrium is deserted.
				
				You begin to feel uneasy.
				
				The ATRIUM is behind you. 
			</description>
			<id>
				officeReception
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				none
				none
				officeAtrium
				none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					Shouldn't be triggered
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
				Washrooms
			</name>
			<description>
				The washrooms are just as luxurious as the atrium you just came from. You note 
				the stylistic change in marble from smooth, creamy white, to deep black with white flecks.
				The gold inlay is just as prevalent, and is now complemented by a host of gold and brass 
				handles, fittings, faucets, and lighting fixtures. 
				
				The ATRIUM is behind you.
			</description>
			<id>
				officeWashrooms
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				none
				none
				officeAtrium
				none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					Shouldn't be triggered
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
				Elevator
			</name>
			<description>
				You step into the elevator. Not surprisingly, it is outfitted with the same 
				taste and expense as the rest of the building. You tap your security pass, and the 
				doors close with a hiss. You feel slightly heavier as the elevetor begins its ascent.
				
				Suddenly, the main lighting shuts down and you are left in the red glow a single emergency
				light set into the ceiling. An alarm starts to sound.
				
				You hear the shriek of tearing steel and your stomach lurches up into your throat as the 
				floor drops from under you. You slam into the roof of the now free falling elevator.
				
				Suddenly everything stops and you slam equally hard against the elevator floor.
				
				Picking yourself up, you see that the mangled elevator doors in front of you leave just enough room
				to slip through them.
			</description>
			<id>
				officeElevator
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				complexHall01
				none
				none
				none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					PASS
					You need your security pass to activate the elevator.
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>		
		<location>
			<name>
				Elevator Hallway
			</name>
			<description>
				You are at the beginning of a long hallway. The alarm still rings in the 
				background, and the entire length of the hall is bathed in rotating red emergency lights.
				
				New debris has rendered the ELEVATOR behind you inaccessible, not that you could use it anyways.
				The rest of the HALLWAY opens up in front of you.
			</description>
			<id>
				complexHall01
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				complexHall02
				none
				none
				none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					Shouldn't be triggered
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>
				Junction Hallway
			</name>
			<description>
				You are roughly in the middle of the hallway. Every time the rotating red lights pass along
				the walls, you can see two doorways, one on each side of you. At the end of the hall you can make 
				out what you believe is an EXIT sign.
				
				The END of the hall is in front of you.
				The BEGINNING of the hall is behind you.
				There is a DOOR to your left.
				There is a DOOR to you right
			</description>
			<id>
				complexHall02
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				none
				complexStorage
				none
				complexLabMain
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					Shouldn't be triggered
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>

			</name>
			<description>
				
			</description>
			<id>
				
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				none
				none
				none
				none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					Shouldn't be triggered
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>
		<location>
			<name>

			</name>
			<description>
				
			</description>
			<id>
				
			</id>
			<items>
			</items>
			<connects>
				none
				none
				none
				none
			</connects>
			<triggers>
				<trigger>
					MUST_HAVE
					NONE
					Shouldn't be triggered
				</trigger>
			</triggers>
		</location>														
	</locations>
	<player>
		<location>
			livingRoom
		</location>
		<items>
			<item>
				<name>
					Toothbrush
				</name>
				<description>
					A TOOTHBRUSH, the thing you use to brush your teeth every couple days or so.
				</description>
				<use>
					Surprisingly you decide to brush your teeth.
				</use>
				<mass>
					1
				</mass>
				<type>
					0
				</type>
				<value>
					1
				</value>
			</item>
		</items>
	</player>
	<history>
	</history>
</game>